name: "CIS 60 - Chapter 10"
questions:
  - question: "What is the software that runs virtual machines called?"
    options:
      - "A) Hypervisor"
      - "B) Virtualizer"
      - "C) Emulator"
      - "D) Simulator"
    answer: "A"
  - question: "Which type of hypervisor loads directly on physical hardware and does not require a separate OS?"
    options:
      - "A) Type 1"
      - "B) Type 2"
      - "C) Both Type 1 and Type 2"
      - "D) Neither Type 1 nor Type 2"
    answer: "A"
  - question: "Which of the following is a widely used Type 2 hypervisor?"
    options:
      - "A) VMware vSphere"
      - "B) Microsoft Hyper-V 2016"
      - "C) Parallels Desktop"
      - "D) XenProject XenServer"
    answer: "C"
  - question: "What is the first step in conducting an investigation with Type 2 Hypervisors?"
    options:
      - "A) Exporting all files associated with VMs"
      - "B) Imaging the host machine"
      - "C) Locating the virtualization software"
      - "D) Recording the hash values of associated files"
    answer: "B"
  - question: "Why are live acquisitions of VMs often necessary?"
    options:
      - "A) To avoid imaging the host machine"
      - "B) To exclude snapshots"
      - "C) To include snapshots"
      - "D) To speed up the investigation process"
    answer: "C"
  - question: "What does the acronym OOV stand for in the context of live acquisitions?"
    options:
      - "A) Order of Volatile Data"
      - "B) Order of Virtual Machines"
      - "C) Order of Operating Systems"
      - "D) Out of Virtualization"
    answer: "A"
  - question: "What is the primary purpose of network forensics?"
    options:
      - "A) To secure a network"
      - "B) To analyze virtual machines"
      - "C) To monitor network traffic"
      - "D) To investigate network attacks"
    answer: "D"
  - question: "Which of the following is a tool used for examining network traffic?"
    options:
      - "A) Mandiant Memoryze"
      - "B) Wireshark"
      - "C) FTK Imager"
      - "D) OSForensics"
    answer: "B"
  - question: "What is a 'honeypot' in network security?"
    options:
      - "A) A tool for analyzing network packets"
      - "B) A type of firewall"
      - "C) A virtual machine used for forensics"
      - "D) A computer that lures attackers"
    answer: "D"
  - question: "What is a Distributed Denial-of-Service (DDoS) attack?"
    options:
      - "A) An attack that exploits weaknesses before patches are available"
      - "B) An attack that hides messages in files"
      - "C) An attack that uses multiple machines to disrupt a network"
      - "D) An attack that targets virtual machines"
    answer: "C"
